awesome awesome AI researcher told New York City we are racing to build our own adversary that's a
big problem people are saying that AI is going to be the replacement probably not now is that
something that's going to happen if it does happen they're going to have to figure this thing out
because what happens when they start displacing excuse me five percent of the workforce let's do
let's do five percent that's a problem uh five percent's an issue we're around four four to five
percent unemployment let's make that 10 let's make it 15 let's make it 16 or 17 and watch what
happens that's horrible that's going to be a really bad place to be so people are taking
artificial intelligence and they're saying hey listen jack we're going to make this your
replacement the issue is is what are these people going to who's going to buy your stuff i still
think that's that's prevalent i don't see people talking about it yeah here's the other side of
that that ugly coin or maybe same side different view if somebody goes out there and creates one